<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on The Common-EGSE Documentation</title>
    <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on The Common-EGSE Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CGSE API Documentation</title>
      <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/api/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 17:23:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/api/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE API Documentation provides the API code documentation that is generated directly from the source docstrings.
 The API docs are generated by pdoc3 as an external source and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.
 The current API documentation corresponds to the CGSE Release 2022.2.15.
 The CGSE API Documentation
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CGSE Interface Control Document</title>
      <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/icd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 17:20:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/icd/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE ICD describes the interfaces between the different components in the system and explains the structure of the different files created by the CGSE.
 The ICD is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.
 The CGSE ICD Documentation
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CGSE User Manual</title>
      <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/user-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:23:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/user-manual/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE User manual is dedicated to test operators and describes all the user type interactions with the different components of the Common-EGSE system.
 The User Manual is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.
 The CGSE User Manual
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CGSE Installation Manual</title>
      <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/installation-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 15:23:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/installation-manual/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE Installation manual is dedicated to system administrators and describes how to install and configure the Common-EGSE system.
 The Installation Manual is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.
 The CGSE Installation Manual
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CGSE Developer Manual</title>
      <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/developer-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 14:23:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/developer-manual/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE Developer manual is dedicated to Python developers who will either contribute to the development of the core CGSE code or who will be developing test house specific device drivers for their test equipment.
 The Developer Manual is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.
 The CGSE Developer Manual
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
