<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Common-EGSE Documentation</title>
    <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Common-EGSE Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Camera Switch ON/OFF</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20230620/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 18:55:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20230620/</guid>
      <description>A small update on the Ground Tests Commanding Manual. We have added a section on how to perform a camera switch on/off from an operator point-of-view.
You can access the manual from this web site if you navigate to the Docs part from the top right, or use the following link: commanding-manual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Commanding Manual added</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20230619/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20230619/</guid>
      <description>We added a new document to this set of CGSE documentation: The Ground Tests Commanding Manual. This is a manual originally written in Microsoft Word, but it was long not updated because the manual became too big and Word too slow to comfortably make changes.
We have updated the content of this manual to match the current system behaviour and functionality. In a future update we will add content that is found necessary while executing the ground tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDF versions added</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/pdfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/pdfs/</guid>
      <description>The PDF version of all the manuals have been added to the site. The PDFs are stand-alone documents and are generated from the sane source as the HTML pages. Some of the inter-document links will however not work with these PDFs.
The CGSE Installation Manual
The CGSE User Manual
The CGSE Developer Manual
The CGSE Interface Control Document</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation Manual updated</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20220630/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 18:21:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20220630/</guid>
      <description>The Installation Manual got a major update. Most of the content from the old website has been transferred and updated, and new content has been added based on experience with installations at IAS. Please note there are still a few sections to fill, that will be done in the coming days.
As you know the manuals are generated from a GitHub repository plato-cgse-doc, so if you read something the is incorrect, or if you notice missing content, please open an issue on the repo or create a pull request with the fixed or updated content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Line Documents</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/on-line-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/on-line-docs/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE documentation has moved and is being updated to include the latest releases for both Common-EGSE and Test Scripts.
You can find the following documents already in a draft version.
Note The links below will bring you to an external page which has no links back into this area. You might want to open the links in another browser tab. The CGSE Installation Manual
The CGSE User Manual</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
