<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CGSE Documentation on The Common-EGSE Documentation</title>
    <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CGSE Documentation on The Common-EGSE Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Camera Switch ON/OFF</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20230620/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 18:55:22 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20230620/</guid>
      <description>A small update on the Ground Tests Commanding Manual. We have added a section on how to perform a camera switch on/off from an operator point-of-view.&#xA;You can access the manual from this web site if you navigate to the Docs part from the top right, or use the following link: commanding-manual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGSE Developer Manual</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/developer-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/developer-manual/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE Developer manual is dedicated to Python developers who will either contribute to the development of the core CGSE code or who will be developing test house specific device drivers for their test equipment.&#xA;The Developer Manual is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.&#xA;The CGSE Developer Manual (HTML) — (PDF)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGSE Interface Control Document</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/icd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/icd/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE ICD describes the interfaces between the different components in the system and explains the structure of the different files created by the CGSE.&#xA;The ICD is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.&#xA;The CGSE Interface Control Document (HTML) — (PDF)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanding Manual added</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20230619/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20230619/</guid>
      <description>We added a new document to this set of CGSE documentation: The Ground Tests Commanding Manual. This is a manual originally written in Microsoft Word, but it was long not updated because the manual became too big and Word too slow to comfortably make changes.&#xA;We have updated the content of this manual to match the current system behaviour and functionality. In a future update we will add content that is found necessary while executing the ground tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ground Tests Commanding Manual</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/commanding-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/commanding-manual/</guid>
      <description>The Ground Tests Commanding Manual is dedicated to site developers and operators who contribute to the PLATO Camera alignment and thermal vacuum testing.&#xA;The Commanding Manual is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.&#xA;The Ground Tests Commanding Manual (HTML) — (PDF)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGSE User Manual</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/user-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/user-manual/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE User manual is dedicated to test operators and describes all the user type interactions with the different components of the Common-EGSE system.&#xA;The User Manual is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.&#xA;The CGSE User Manual (HTML) — (PDF)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDF versions added</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/pdfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/pdfs/</guid>
      <description>The PDF version of all the manuals have been added to the site. The PDFs are stand-alone documents and are generated from the sane source as the HTML pages. Some of the inter-document links will however not work with these PDFs.&#xA;The CGSE Installation Manual&#xA;The CGSE User Manual&#xA;The CGSE Developer Manual&#xA;The CGSE Interface Control Document</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGSE API Documentation</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/api/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE API Documentation provides the API code documentation that is generated directly from the source docstrings.&#xA;The API docs are generated by pdoc3 as an external source and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.&#xA;The current API documentation corresponds to the CGSE Release 2023.37.0.&#xA;The CGSE API Documentation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGSE Installation Manual</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/installation-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/installation-manual/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE Installation manual is dedicated to system administrators and describes how to install and configure the Common-EGSE system.&#xA;The Installation Manual is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.&#xA;The CGSE Installation Manual (HTML) — (PDF)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installation Manual updated</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20220630/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 18:21:12 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/update-20220630/</guid>
      <description>The Installation Manual got a major update. Most of the content from the old website has been transferred and updated, and new content has been added based on experience with installations at IAS. Please note there are still a few sections to fill, that will be done in the coming days.&#xA;As you know the manuals are generated from a GitHub repository plato-cgse-doc, so if you read something the is incorrect, or if you notice missing content, please open an issue on the repo or create a pull request with the fixed or updated content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Line Documents</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/on-line-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/on-line-docs/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE documentation has moved and is being updated to include the latest releases for both Common-EGSE and Test Scripts.&#xA;You can find the following documents already in a draft version.&#xA;Note The links below will bring you to an external page which has no links back into this area. You might want to open the links in another browser tab. The CGSE Installation Manual&#xA;The CGSE User Manual</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ivs-kuleuven.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/about/</guid>
      <description>Although we try hard to write good and clean code, we feel the need to provide documentation about the Common-EGSE on several levels.&#xA;In GitHub issues, during installations and integrated system tests we are asked similar questions at each occasion. We try therefore to focus the documentation on this site to pragmatic and hands-on instructions and explanations of the Common-EGSE and the Test Scripts.&#xA;The documentation that is made available on this site is broken up in the following manuals:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
