<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Common-EGSE Documentation</title>
    <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Common-EGSE Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 14:23:07 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CGSE Developer Manual</title>
      <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/developer-manual/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 14:23:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/docs/developer-manual/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE Developer manual is dedicated to Python developers who will either contribute to the development of the core CGSE code or who will be developing test house specific device drivers for their test equipment.
 The Developer Manual is an external document generated by AsciiDoctor and accessible from this site. You might want to open the link in a new browser tab.
 The CGSE Developer Manual
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Line Documents</title>
      <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/on-line-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 13:31:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/posts/on-line-docs/</guid>
      <description>The CGSE documentation has moved and is being updated to include the latest releases for both Common-EGSE and Test Scripts.
 You can find the following documents already in a draft version.
   Note  The links below will bring you to an external page which has no links back into this area. You might want to open the links in another browser tab.       The CGSE Installation Manual</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rhuygen.github.io/plato-cgse-doc/about/</guid>
      <description>Although we try hard to write good and clean code, we feel the need to provide documentation about the Common-EGSE on several levels.
 In GitHub issues, during installations and integrated system tests we are asked similar questions at each occasion. We try therefore to focus the documentation on this site to pragmatic and hands-on instructions and explanations of the Common-EGSE and the Test Scripts.
 The documentation that is made available on this site is broken up in the following manuals:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
